# **CONTACT**

- 908-370-6530
- github.com/MaxFrank13
- maxfrank13@gmail.com
- www.franklymaxwell.com
- linkedin.com/in/maxwell-frank/

### MAXWELL FRANK

Frontend Web Developer

Lifetime creator with a background in woodworking and restaurant industries recently making a transition into Web Development. By calling on this personal experience, I provide a unique perspective on the construction of web pages and applications. I find the logistical challenges that programming presents to be a motivating force in my experience as a developer.

### SKILLS

- GIT
- HTML/CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- JQUERY
- BOOTSTRAP
- BULMA
- THREEJS

# **ATTRIBUTES**

- MOTIVATED
- PERSONABLE
- LEADER
- PROBLEM SOLVER
- ANIMATED

### **EDUCATION**

### Summit High School

2007-2011

Senior Student Humanities Award 2011 Wheeler Family Bowling Scholarship 2011

# University of New Hampshire

2011-2015, 2021-2022 Studied Sociology 2015 UNH Coding Bootcamp 2022

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Falafel Mafia, Portland ME - Cook/Assistant Manager 2019 – 2021

Cooking to order in a fast-paced environment. Working on food truck and experience with mobile food services.

# Hanson Woodturning, Kennebunkport ME - Craftsman 2017-2019

Use of milling machines and experience turning raw material into high end finished product. Attention to fine details.

# Richardson Allen, Biddeford ME – Woodworker 2016

Experience with packing and shipping off final product. Use of sprayer to apply marine quality paint.

### **PROJECTS**

#### CarryOn

Use of OpenTripMap and Unsplash APIs to provide users with a method for obtaining the best features to visit while on vacation. Technologies used: HTML/CSS, jQuery, Bulma, Fetch API

### **Electric Slide**

Simple platformer game with vibrant animations. Technologies used: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Canvas API

### **Weather Dashboard**

A weather dashboard for viewing upcoming forecasts of selected locations. Technologies used: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, OpenWeather API, Clay.css

### **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

Endurance skateboarding
Hiking & the outdoors
Video games & design